{
    "subject": "resource/Jack_Dempsey_(politician)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Australian politician",
    "human_readable": "The description of Jack Dempsey (politician) is an Australian politician.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8774481415748596,
            "question": "What is Jack Dempsey's current role in Australian politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808987498283386,
            "question": "Is Jack Dempsey involved in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6100475788116455,
            "question": "Is Jack Dempsey known for any particular achievements in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5796605944633484,
            "question": "What political party does Jack Dempsey belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5487146377563477,
            "question": "Where is Jack Dempsey from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5413979291915894,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Jack Dempsey's political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5405836701393127,
            "question": "What profession does Jack Dempsey have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.531406581401825,
            "question": "What country is Jack Dempsey from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4712567627429962,
            "question": "Are there any notable policies or positions associated with Jack Dempsey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4236395061016083,
            "question": "Has Jack Dempsey held any elected office?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The description of Jack Dempsey (politician) is an Australian politician.",
            "html": "dbpedia_739_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable policies or positions associated with Jack Dempsey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_739_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Jack Dempsey from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_739_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Jack Dempsey have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_739_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_739_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, particularly the one in `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_739/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt`, Jack Dempsey (politician) is described as a former Liberal National party state minister and a Bundaberg mayor, which implies that he is also an Australian politician."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that Jack Dempsey is described as a 58-year-old Australian Politician, which supports the statement that Jack Dempsey is an Australian politician."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}